All's my life I has to fight, nigga All's my life I, hard times like, yeah
Bad trips like, yeah Nazareth, I'm fucked up, homie you fucked up
But if God got us then we gon' be alright
Nigga we gon' be alright Nigga we gon' be alright
We gon' be alright Do you hear me, do you feel me?
We gon' be alright Nigga we gon' be alright
Do you hear me, do you feel me?
We gon' be alright
Uh, and when I wake up I recognize you looking at me for the pay cut
Bahamas I be looking at you from the face down
Why Mack 11 even rule with the face down?
Schemin', now let me tell you about my life
Painkillers only put me in a twilight
Where pretty pussy and Benjamin is the highlight
Now tell my mama I love her but this what I like, Lord knows
20 of 'em in my Chevy, tell 'em all to come and get me
Reaping everything I sow, so my karma come in heaven
No preliminary hearings on my record
I'm a motherfucking gangsta in silence for the record, uh
Tell the world I know it's too late
Boys and girls I think I've gone crazy
Trying to decide my prices all day
Won't you please believe when I say
Wouldn't you know, we been hurt, been down before
Nigga, when our pride was low
Looking at the world like, where do we go?
Nigga, and we hate pro-poor
When the killers dead and the street was sure
Nigga, I met the preacher's door
My knees getting weak and my gun might blow
But we gon' be alright
Nigga, we gon' be alright
We gon' be alright
Do you hear me? Do you feel me?
Nigga, we gon' be alright
Huh? We gon' be alright
Do you hear me? Do you feel me?
We gon' be alright
What you want? You a house? You a car?
You got the acres and the mule, a piano, a guitar?
Anything, see my name is Lucy, I'm your dog
Motherfucker, you can live at the mall
I can see the evil, I can tell it
I know it's illegal, I don't think about it
I deposit every other zero
Thinking of my partner, put the candy painting on a Rico
Digging in my pocket, ain't a profit
Big enough to feed you, everyday my logic
Get another dollar just to keep you in the presence of your Chico
Ah!
I don't talk about it, be about it
Everyday I sequel, if I got it, then you know you got it
Heaven, I can reach you
Pet dog, pet dog, pet dog, my dog, that's all
Big back and chat, I trap the bag for y'all
I rap, I black on track, so rest assured
My rights, my wrongs, I write 'til I'm right with God
When you know, we been hurt, been down before
Nigga, when our pride was low
Looking at the world like, "Where do we go?"
Nigga, and we hate po' po'
One to kill is dead in the street for sure
Nigga, I'm at the preacher's door
My knees getting weak and my gun might blow
But we gon' be alright
Nigga, we gon' be alright
We gon' be alright
Do you hear me? Do you feel me? We gon' be alright
Nigga, we gon' be alright
Huh? We gon' be alright
Do you hear me? Do you feel me? We gon' be alright
I keep my head up, my eyebrows smile
I pray you won't deny
Love me is complicated
Too afraid of life changes
I'm alright in your favor
Dark nights and my prayers