The sun goes down, the stars come out And all that comes is here and now
My universe will never be the same I'm glad you came
You cast a spell on me, spell on me You hid me like the sky fell on me, fell on me
And I decided you look well on me, well on me So let's go somewhere no one else can see you and me
Turn the lights out now, now I'll take you by the hand Hand you another drink, drink it if you can
Can you spend a little time, time is slipping away Away from us so stay, stay with me I can make, make you glad you came
The sun goes down, the stars come out And all that comes is here and now
My universe will never be the same I'm glad you came, I'm glad you came
You cast a spell on me, spell on me You hid me like the sky fell on me, fell on me
And I decided you look well on me, well on me So let's go somewhere no one else can see you and me
Turn the lights out now, now I'll take you by the hand Hand you another drink, drink it if you can
Can you spend a little time, time is slipping away Away from us so stay, stay with me I can make, make you glad you came
The sun goes down, the stars come out And all that comes is here and now
My universe will never be the same I'm glad you came, I'm glad you came
I'm glad you came
The sun goes down, the stars come out And all that comes is here and now
My universe will never be the same I'm glad you came, I'm glad you came
King
[BLANK_AUDIO]